//question list used in the script.js with the question, answer selection and answers
var questionList = [
    {
        question: 'How to select the elements with the class name "example"?',
        answerSelection: ['example','#example','.example','Class example'],
        answer:'.example'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following CSS property is used to specify the space between every letter inside an element?',
        answerSelection: ['alpha-spacing','character-spacing','letter-spacing','alphabet-spacing'],
        answer: 'letter-spacing'
    },
    {
        question: 'The CSS property used to specigy the transparency of an element is -',
        answerSelection: ['opacity','filter','visibility','overlay'],
        answer: 'opacity'
    },
    {
        question: 'The CSS property used to make the text bold is -',
        answerSelection: ['font-weight:bold','weight: bold','font: bold','style: bold'],
        answer: 'font-weight:bold'
    },
    {
        question: 'The HTML attribute used to define the internal stylesheet is -',
        answerSelection: ['style','<style>','<link>','<script>'],
        answer:'<style>'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following is the correct syntax for referring the external style sheet?',
        answerSelection: ['<style src = example.css>','<style src = "example.css" >','<stylesheet> example.css </stylesheet>','<link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css" href="example.css">'],
        answer: '<link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css" href="example.css">'
    },
    {
        question: 'CSS stands for -',
        answerSelection: ['Cascade style sheets','Color and style sheets','Cascading style sheets','None of the above'],
        answer: 'Cascading style sheets'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following is not a type of combinator?',
        answerSelection: ['>','~','+','*'],
        answer: '*'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following CSS property specifies the origin of the background-image?',
        answerSelection: ['background-origin','background-attachment','background-size','None of the above'],
        answer: 'background-origin'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which if the following CSS function allows us to perform calculations?',
        answerSelection: ['calc() function','calculator() function','calculate() function','cal() function'],
        answer: 'calc() function'
    }
]